all ready guys welcome back and in this video I'm going to show you a really
一切准备就绪家伙欢迎回来 ，并在此 视频我真的要告诉你
cool way to get the most frequently occurring item in a list but before we
很酷的 方式 来获得 最频繁的 在列表中但在我们之前发生的项目
do I just want to give a quick shout out to Caleb Haslam and Nathan Bradley they
我只是想快速 喊出来 他们是Caleb Haslam 和Nathan Bradley
each contributed 5 bucks to my patreon account I love you guys I want to have
每个贡献了5美元给我的patreon 帐户我爱你们我想要的人
your babies and yeah let's get on to the tutorial all right so let's say that we
你的孩子，是的，让我们到 教程没事让我们说 ，我们
have any list but in this tutorial let me go ahead and copy this alright so there we go so I just have this chunk of
有任何列表但在本教程中让我们 我继续 这样 复制这个好吧 我们走 ，所以我只是 有这个块
text right here and I'll remember huh I don't even remember where I pasted this
文字就在这里， 我会记得我 甚至不记得我粘贴的地方
from somewhere maybe on my website or something but we have any text you can have any list and we want to get the
从某个地方 可能在我的网站或 但是我们有任何文字可以 有任何清单，我们想得到
words that occur most frequently maybe my PR guy was yelling at me he's like
最常出现的词可能是 我的公关人员对我大吼大叫他就像
dude you save the same words over and over again and I probably do so how can we do that well we can write our own
老兄你把同样的话保存在 再一次，我可能会这样做，怎么可能 我们做得很好， 我们可以写自己的
custom function or I'll show you guys a cool little module so from collections
自定义功能或我会告诉你们一个 来自收藏品的酷小模块
we're going to import the class counter so this is gonna this is actually pretty
我们要导入班级计数器 所以这真的很漂亮
cool class if you want to dive deeper well what it essentially does is you
如果你 想深入潜水， 那就 很酷 以及它本质上是做什么的
pass it in a list and then you can run a bunch of cool statistics on it now we
将它传递给列表然后你 可以运行一个 现在我们一堆很酷的统计数据
already have one issue and that's that this right here is just a big ol long
已经有 一个问题 就是这样 这就是一个很长的时间
string we actually need to convert all of these words into a list so in order
字符串我们实际上需要转换所有 这些词成 一个列表 ，以便为了
to do that it's actually really easy just say words you can name your
这样做实际上 很容易 刚才说的话你能说出 你的
variable anything you want of course for this text string in order to make it
你当然要为变什么 这个文本字符串， 以使它
individual a list of words all you do is your right split so that it breaks up a
个人所有你做的单词列表 你的 权利分裂，以便 它 分手了
string into a list so now we have a list that's I don't know like maybe 50 words
字符串到一个列表，所以现在我们有一个列表 我不知道那可能是50个单词
long or whatever and just to show you guys real quick just print this out
很长或什么，只是为了告诉 你 家伙真正的快 刚 打印出来
alright so now we can see that we have a list look at that looking good so now
好吧，现在我们可以看到 我们有一个 列表看看那个好看 所以现在
that we have a list we want to get the most frequently occurring word so how do
我们有一个我们想要的清单 最常出现的词是怎么做的
we do that well let me just make a just name a counter wine
我们做得 很好，让我 做 一个公正的 说一个反酒
and I'm going to set this equal to counter which is an object from the
而我将把它设置为等于 计数器，它是一个对象 从
counter class or an instance is the proper term so whenever we initialize
计数器类或实例是 正确的术语， 所以每当我们初始化
this what we do is we pass in a list so what that's going to do is it's going to
我们所做的就是传递一个清单 那是什么要做 的是它会
say this is our object run a bunch of statistics about this list just
说这是我们的对象 运行 一堆 这个名单 只是统计
essentially this right here so boom roasted it did that now once it's
基本上 就在这里如此繁荣 烤了它现在做了一次它
initialized we can just you know print out whatever we want so let's say that
初始化我们可以只知道打印 无论我们想要什么， 所以让我们说
we want the top three occurring words well for counter which was our object
我们想要 前三个出现的单词 很好的柜台，这是我们的目标
there is a function called most common now inside here we can just write any
有一个 叫做最常见 的功能 现在在这里，我们可以 写任何
number we want a 3 5 whatever I'm going to say 3 and that's going to give me the
号码我们想要 什么，不管我要去哪里 说3 ，那会给我的
3 most common words in that list so now I'll just print top 3 and there we go so
现在，该列表中 最常见的3个 单词 我就打印前 3 名 ，有我们 这么 走
this is actually pretty cool it returns a list of tuples and the tupple has two
这 真的很酷， 它返回 元组列表和tupple有两个
parts to it the first one is of course the word itself the item in the list and
它的第一 部分当然是 第一部分 单词本身 是 列表中 的项目
the second one is the frequency counter so this says hey these are your three
第二个是频率计数器 所以这说嘿这些是你的三个
most common occurring words the you wrote 5 times 2 euro 4 and in was in
最常见的发生的 话 ，你 写了5次2欧元4和in in
your list 3 times so a lot of awesome information so there you go again a real
你的清单3次，所以 非常棒 信息，所以你再去一个真实的
quick tutorial but definitely useful and again there's a lot more to this counter
快速教程，但绝对有用 再次，这个柜台还有很多
class but now that I you know got your guys a feet a little bit wet you can dive in a little more if you want thank
上课，但现在我知道了你的 伙计们，你的 脚 有点湿 如果你 想要感谢，请 再多一点
you guys for watching I'll see you guys next time
你们看着我们会见到 你们 下次